Mayowa Shoyinka

18, Taiwo Kolawole Avenue, Unity Estate, Bodore, Ajah, Lagos Nigeria, | 07013137863, 08146266819 | mayowas29@gmail.com

Professional Summary

An expert in attracting, retaining and maintaining strong relationships with clients and improving sales and revenue, with almost 3 years of related experience and advanced skills. Always looking for ways to improve productivity and customer satisfaction with exceptional service. Maintaining well-organized and presentable work areas always. Well organized, Passionate, ambitious and driven person. Good team-player, who is ready to apply her knowledge with room for growth and advancement as a professional web-developer.

Skills

- * Well versed in Microsoft Office [Word, Excel, Power-point] and PowerBI.
- * Well versed in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, WordPress, Bootstrap, React.js.
- * Good communication, team-player, leadership and teamwork skill.

Result

Second Class Lower Division (2:2)

Training

Junior Software Engineer 07/2020 to present

Dufuna CodeCamp –Lagos, Nigeria

Power BI Analytics Academy –Lagos, Niger

03/2020 to 04/2020

Experience

Internship

Worksson - Stockholm, Sweeden

07/2021 to 07/2021

- * Developed new frontend and backend features
- *Customized and improved existing system service

Training Coordinator

IT360 Academy – Ibadan, Oyo, Nigeria

12/2019 to 03/2020

- * Assessed training needs for new and existing students.
- * Facilitated students' enrollment and certification.
- * Managed faculties, developed curriculum, training aids (manuals and handbooks) and remained up to date in the development within the industry.
- * Organized and developed training programs to meet specific training needs.
- * Developed marketing Plans for iT360 Academy training courses.
- * Established and maintained relationships, partnership with stakeholders in the tech space.

- * Designed assessment tools to measure training effectiveness.
- * Tracked and reported training outcomes and provided feedbacks to the management.

Business Development Officer

STEINSERVE INNOVATIONS – Ibadan, OYO, Nigeria

04/2019 to 09/2019

- * Developed and implemented growth opportunities for Steinserve.
- * Created long term value for Steinserve from students and customers.
- * Performed market research to identify new opportunities and establish strategies for pursuing them to a successful logical conclusion.
- * Developed and delivered pitches for potential investors.
- * Mentored and counseled students for career prospect, technical and financial support.

Account/Supervising Officer

Nelseno Hotel- Abacha Road, Nasarawa, Nigeria

12/2018 to 01/2019

* Handled logistics and account of the hotel and also supervised every departments in the hotel.

Technical Support Officer/ Helpdesk Assistant

African Independent Television – Abuja, Federal Capital Territory, Nigeria 08/2018 to 11/2018

- * Worked on numerous training systems and repaired different hardware components in the system unit.
- * Created various computer connectors and developed computer networks.
- * Facilitated the installation of computer software and packages for different department.
- * In-charge of all department calls and provided basic solutions to all other department(s).

Assistant Trainer/Facility Officer

Harmony Innovation Hub – Abuja, Federal Capital Territory, Nigeria

02/2018 to 07/2018

- * Planned and Trained new intakes, interns and staffs on various courses held in the company
- * Worked hand in hand with the other company trainer to download textbooks and materials for Harmony e-library learning suit.
- * Led a team in the installation of a software used by micro-finance called Mifos accounting system
- * Worked with the software department in developing various applications.

Education

Bachelor of Science: Computer Science (ICT Option)

02/2013 to 07/2018

Ajayi Crowther University - Oyo, Oyo Sate, Nigeria

West African Senior School Certificate: Maverick College Ibadan - Ibadan, Oyo, Nigeria 07/2011